giftxoxo.com 2016-12-19

# Privacy Policy, personal information details

We value the trust you place in Giftxoxo.com. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for your secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

  * By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy read with Terms and Conditions of Giftxoxo.com. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website.
  * By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms and Conditions of Giftxoxo.com.

### Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

Giftxoxo keeps a track of your information to offer you the best possible gifting experience. Before completing your gifting process we collect personally identifiable information (i.e. email address, name, phone number, etc.) from you when you set up an account with Giftxoxo.com. While you can browse some sections of our Site without being a registered member, certain activities do require registration. You can see, review and change your personal information through the Application. Further, we or our associate companies may use your email address to notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information based on your previous orders and interests. Emails are sent only to Giftxoxo members who have chosen to receive them (opted-in) or who have made a purchase on our website. At any time, you can notify us, if you wish to stop receiving these emails. We may also ask you for information regarding your personal preferences and demographics to help us better meet your needs. If you have any valuable suggestion, please feel free to e-mail us on cs@Giftxoxo.com 

### Use of Demographic and Profile Data

When you place any order for a gift on our Site, we may collect various information to process and fulfill your order in an efficient manner. We collect, store and process your data for processing your order on the Site and any possible later claims, and to provide you with our services. We may collect your title, name, gender, email address, postal address, delivery address (if different), telephone number, mobile number, fax number, payment details, payment card details or bank account details. 

We need this information to allow you to go ahead with placing your order for a gift. We may use the data (provided by you) to process payment for the gift and deliver the gift to you. We also use that data to inform you when the product is about to be delivered. 

We may pass your name and address on to a third party in order to make delivery of the product to you (for example to our courier or supplier). We may also share your data with our franchisor. You further authorise the franchisor to use this information to sell products to you, directly or indirectly. 

Your actual order details may be stored with us and you may access this information by logging into your account on the Site. Here you can view the details of your orders that have been completed, those which are open and those which are shortly to be dispatched and administer your address details, bank details and any newsletter to which you may have subscribed. You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault. 

We shall not share any of your personal information with third parties without your explicit consent. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent and we only use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. We view protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and Your Information is one of our most important assets. We store and process Your Information on computers located in the India that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. We use third parties to verify and certify our privacy principles. If you object to your Information being transferred or used in this way please do not use the site. 

Under no circumstances we do rent, trade or share your personal information that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure. 

### Cookies

The acceptance of cookies is not a requirement for visiting the Site. However we would like to point out that, some functionality on the Site and ordering is only possible with the activation of cookies. A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. Giftxoxo.com places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. You hereby accept our assurance that Giftxoxo.com's cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information and are free from viruses. 

### Sharing of personal information

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and partners to help, detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in. 

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public. 

Giftxoxo.com and its partners will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity in case we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity and whenever such a transaction occurs, then such other business entity (or the new combined entity) would be required to follow these privacy policies with respect to your personal information. 

### Link to Other Sites

This Application may utilize social networking or share functionality or may contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by Giftxoxo. Giftxoxo has no control over any share functionality or the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party site. You are subject to the policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to anyone. 

### Security Precautions

We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorised or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction or damage to your information. When we collect data through the Site, we collect your personal details on a secure server. We use firewalls on our servers. When we collect payment card details electronically, we use encryption by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) coding. Whilst we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in unencrypted electronic communications with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of your identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. 

### Content

By submitting data to us or our agent or while using the Site, you personally gives your consent and right to our use of your data in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. 

### Copyright

We have copyright over this Privacy Policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purposes is not allowed. Infringements may be subject to legal action. 

This Privacy Policy can change at any time to include / exclude clauses and Giftxoxo.com does not bear any responsibility for updating Users on the same. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

Giftxoxo.com provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account. If you want to remove your contact information from all Giftxoxo.com lists and newsletters, please email to cs@giftxoxo.com 

### Advertisements on Giftxoxo.com

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

### Questions

If there are any queries with in regard to the Private Policies mentioned hereinabove, the same can be directed to the following address: [careers@giftxoxo.com](mailto:careers@giftxoxo.com)
